http://www.eddieherr.com/purchase-policy

Safer Campus Initiative
IMG Academy continues to use the utmost of caution when it comes to the health and safety of everyone on campus. We have been following guidelines recommended by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), Johns Hopkins All Children's Hospital as well as the Florida Department of Health.
View our SAFER CAMPUS PROTOCOLS to learn how we are making campus a safer place for everyone.
Or, choose an area of interest below to learn about general COVID-19 information for each area of interest.
Boarding School Students & Parents
Campers & Parents / Visiting Teams / Event Operators & Participants & Professional Athletes
Legacy Hotel / Academy Park Villas / Lodge & Bollettieri Resort Villas
IMG Academy Golf Club
John Hopkins All Children's Hospital / Gatorade Sport Science Institute
Previous Updates
Stay Updated on the Virus
Prevention & Resources
Employees
Eddie Herr International Junior Championship
November 24, 2020 - December 6, 2020 CANCELLEDTennis
Add to Calendar
2020-11-24T18:59:21-05:00
2020-12-06T18:59:21-05:00
Eddie Herr International Junior Championship
https://www.imgacademy.com/events/eddie-herr-international-junior-championship
5650 Bollettieri Blvd. Bradenton FL, 34210
ShareEvent
Event Overview
The Eddie Herr International Junior Championship at IMG Academy welcomes over 2,000 junior tennis players from over 90 countries! This elite tournament attracts the world's most competitive tennis players. Many current professionals not only have participated but have also won this tournament including: Maria Sharapova, Jelena Jankovic, Whitney Osuigwe, Miomir Kecmanovic, Michael Mmoh, Andy Roddick, Xavier Malisse and many more.
IMPORTANT COVID-19 UPDATE (AS OF 9/30/20)
The health and safety of everyone involved in the Eddie Herr International Junior Championship remains our top priority, so due to global health concerns regarding COVID-19 (coronavirus), and in agreement with the USTA, this year’s event will not take place. We thank our guests, players, partners and staff for their support, and look forward to welcoming everyone back to Eddie Herr in 2021.
2019 12s, 14s, and 16s Results
2019 18s Results
Location
5650 Bollettieri Blvd. Bradenton FL, 34210
Get Directions
Venue
IMG AcademyExplore Venue
Stay & Play
The Legacy Hotel at IMG Academy is the ultimate accommodation for IMG events. Participants and spectators will enjoy a modern suite of luxury amenities at this lifestyle, boutique hotel - all within walking distance from the IMG Academy campus. Recover in our 24-hour fitness center or by our resort-style pool, connect over a meal at Icon Eatery & Bar or Icon Loft, and rejuvenate with Wellness Spa treatment options and in-room dining.
Competition Format
The Eddie Herr International Tennis Tournament is an invitation only event. Limited to 128 qualifying draws and 64 main draws per age group, the tournament is host to over 2000 junior tennis players from over 90 countries.
Official Ball of The Eddie Herr International
IMG Academy and Dunlop have partnered together to provide players with the most optimal training and development experience available in today's game. Our players utilize the same quality of hard and clay court balls as the professional tours. IMG Academy is a primary location for the testing of all current and future Dunlop products, so athletes have the opportunity to utilize cutting-edge technology and equipment right from campus.
Fees & Tickets
Players
The 2020 Eddie Herr has been cancelled due to COVID-19.
Important Links & Forms
USTA Membership
UTR Link
Event Map
Housing Form
Contact
General Inquiries
[email protected]
Registration & Eligibility
Registration for the 2020 Eddie Herr International Junior Championship has been cancelled due to COVID-19.
The
Eddie Herr Tennis Tournament utilizes UTR’s (Universal Tennis Rating) for consideration into the qualifying draw and main draw of the tournament.
When applying for the tournament, please make sure to have your UTR information readily available to input into the application.
If your country does not accept the UTR system, please contact us at [email protected] for more information on how to apply or qualify.
Everyone is required to have a USTA membership in order to sign-up for the Eddie Herr Tournament. Please click here for registration instructions through the USTA.
The Eddie Herr International Junior Championship is a selection-based tournament. Application submission does not guarantee entry into the tournament. There are only 128 qualifying draw invites and 64 main draw invites per group.
U.S. and foreign players are eligible per the USTA age requirements.
16 & under- born in 2004 or 2005 (must be 15 or 16 on December 31, 2020).
14 & under - born in 2006 or 2007 (must be 13 or 14 on December 31, 2020).
12 & under - born in 2008 or 2009 (must be 11 or 12 on December 31, 2020). Athletes 10 years old or younger will NOT be considered for acceptance into the tournament.
Book Your Camp
Online Camp Builder
Chat
close
1
Options
2 Camp
3 Customize
Enter your info to start the camp registration
process
Email already entered!
Register Now
summary
close
1 Options
2 Camp
3 Customize
$0
Camp Subtotal
Add to
Cart
Ready to Leave so Soon?
PRO TIP: Add a camp to your cart to review later
Continue  Close
Travel & Planning
Rental Cars
Enterprise Rent-A-Car promotes an easy-to-use service and has two pickup/drop-off centers within 10 miles of the IMG Academy campus.
Rent a Car
Airport Transportation
IMG Academy offers dropoff and pickup services for all local Florida airports. Teams and players can schedule arranged transportation through Travel and Planning on IMG Academy’s website.
Schedule Pickup
Local Airports
Sarasota/Bradenton Florida is conveniently located in central Florida and located near many large international airports. Make sure to book travel through one of these local airports.
Local Airports
Local Attractions
Florida’s premier theme parks are located just minutes away from IMG Academy.
Visit Walt Disney World, Busch Gardens, Universal Studios or the Tampa Bay Rays to experience Florida.
Performance Based Nutrition
Dining on campus provides athletes with a full balanced nutritional diet designed for athletes competing at the highest level.
Options include buffet style and made to order menus for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
Learn More
Retail
Visit the Official Online Store of IMG Academy at shopimg.com, your IMG Academy branded gear headquarters. On campus shopping also available in the IMG Academy Campus Center’s bookstore.
Shop Now
IMG Academy Events Proudly Sponsored By
Event Hosting & Sponsorships
Call
Email
Visit Us
Contact Us
For enrollment & program registration
1-800-872-6425
For all other inquires
1-866-300-4538
[email protected]
5650 Bollettieri BLVD.Bradenton, FL 34210
Host or Sponsor an Event at IMG Academy
By clicking Submit you agree to and have read our privacy policy: Privacy Policy
Visit Us
Are you interested in touring the IMG Academy campus? Fill out the form below to submit a tour request and we will be in touch soon to confirm your request.
By clicking Visit Us! you agree to and have read our privacy policy: Privacy Policy
Loading...
contact us
For enrollment & program registration
1-800-872-6425
For all other inquires
1-866-300-4538
[email protected]
5650 Bollettieri BLVD.Bradenton, FL 34210
Location & Offices
Chat with an Advisor!
In chatting with an advisor you agree to and have read our privacy policy: Privacy Policy
Request Consultation
A specialized expert will follow up within 24 hours.
By clicking Submit you agree to and have read our privacy policy: Privacy Policy
Loading...
Visit Us
Are you interested in touring the IMG Academy campus? Fill out the form below to submit a tour request and we will be in touch soon to confirm your request.
By clicking Visit Us! you agree to and have read our privacy policy: Privacy Policy
Loading...
Connect:
FIRSTFORM, Inc.
Filter results:
[email protected]
5650 Bollettieri BLVD.Bradenton, FL 34210
